{
    "subject": "resource/L\u00e1szl\u00f3_Tas\u00f3",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Hungarian_People's_Republic",
    "human_readable": "L\u00e1szl\u00f3 Tas\u00f3 was born in Hungarian People's Republic.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9391584396362305,
            "question": "Is L\u00e1szl\u00f3 Tas\u00f3 Hungarian?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9225501418113708,
            "question": "In what country was L\u00e1szl\u00f3 Tas\u00f3 born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9204522371292114,
            "question": "Where was L\u00e1szl\u00f3 Tas\u00f3 born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8708323836326599,
            "question": "What was the name of the political entity where L\u00e1szl\u00f3 Tas\u00f3 was born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8200579285621643,
            "question": "What year was L\u00e1szl\u00f3 Tas\u00f3 born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6744612455368042,
            "question": "What is L\u00e1szl\u00f3 Tas\u00f3 known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6609012484550476,
            "question": "Who were some influential people in L\u00e1szl\u00f3 Tas\u00f3's life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4550514221191406,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about L\u00e1szl\u00f3 Tas\u00f3's life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4125955104827881,
            "question": "What impact did L\u00e1szl\u00f3 Tas\u00f3 have on the world?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3879505395889282,
            "question": "What significant events happened during L\u00e1szl\u00f3 Tas\u00f3's lifetime?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=L\u00e1szl\u00f3 Tas\u00f3 was born in Hungarian People's Republic.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7088_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What impact did L\u00e1szl\u00f3 Tas\u00f3 have on the world?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7088_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about L\u00e1szl\u00f3 Tas\u00f3's life?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7088_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who were some influential people in L\u00e1szl\u00f3 Tas\u00f3's life?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7088_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7088_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7088_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7088_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7088_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7088_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7088_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7088_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7088_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7088_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7088_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nThe provided text doesn't mention where L\u00e1szl\u00f3 Tas\u00f3 was born.  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON response:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this response is that the documents do not mention L\u00e1szl\u00f3 Tas\u00f3's birthplace, let alone a specific mention of being born in the Hungarian People's Republic. The only information provided about L\u00e1szl\u00f3 Tas\u00f3 is his career and activities as a public official in Hungary, but no details are given about his personal life or place of birth."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The provided context does not contain any information about L\u00e1szl\u00f3 Tas\u00f3's place of birth. Therefore, we cannot confirm or deny the statement that he was born in the Hungarian People's Republic based on the given documents."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}